There are indeed many suspicious things
about Wen Yanhui's past.
His original name is Chen Hui.
Back in the last century,
he was a famous male model
at the Xinggang Dance Hall.
There, he met
the richest woman in Xinggang
at the time, Wen Yan.
Wen Yan fell in love with Chen Hui
at first sight.
She insisted on marrying him
despite the rumors,
and gave birth to a child, Wen Xin.
She also brought him into
the Wen Group,
which she founded single-handedly.
But a few years later,
on the eve of the board election,
Wen Yan was involved in a traffic accident
and died unexpectedly.
To commemorate his late wife, Chen Hui
changed his name to Wen Yanhui.
And the Wen Group
completely became his property.
A familiar car accident,
and a familiar accidental death.
It's highly likely that
he climbed the ladder step by step,
relying on women.
Now everyone says
the Wen Group belongs to Wen Yanhui.
But no one remembers
that this Group was built by a woman.
There aren't that many accidents
in this world.
Hao,
go find out
what exactly happened to Wen Yan's death.
So,
this is what you care about
the most right now?
Boss died for you.
Why aren't you sad at all?
Jiang Yu and I
are great partners.
And I believe he'll be fine.
Before the explosion,
he must have already left the factory.
But we can't find him.
Jiang Yu is a great partner.
If he really had an accident,
I'd be very sorry too.
But Hao,
I have to apologize to you.
I have to continue.
I have to continue
and find all the killers
who murdered Jiang Yuqing
and make them pay.
This is something
I owe myself
and your Boss.
Boss is so foolish.
How could he fall in love with
such a cold and ruthless woman like you?
There is something Boss left for you
in the secret room.
I will continue to investigate
Wen Yan's case.
Actually, before the operation,
Boss had already made a will.
If anything happened to him,
the entire Cloudsea would be yours.
From now on,
I will also take orders from you.
This is what I owe Boss.
[Dearest Episode 14]
To my love, Jianan,
I have been drawn to you my whole life.
From a brief encounter at 16,
I unconsciously fell in love with you.
When my mother had a car accident,
all the evidence pointed to you.
I could only hide my love
and approach you again.
I once thought
getting close to you again
was for revenge.
Only later did I realize
that meeting you
was the luckiest twist of fate in my life.
I left everything I have to you.
But what I want to leave you most
is a clean version of myself
and a real wedding.
One day,
if I can truly become your groom,
I hope
we will no longer have hatred
or secrets at that time.
Only love
can connect our hearts.
Jiang Yu, I will definitely find you.
Jianan, Jianan.
Miss Mingzhu.
Don't push yourself, Alex.
What are you doing here?
Long time no see.
The last time I saw you was in Cloudsea.
At that time, you were drinking with me.
So what do you want to say?
Of course I want to cure you.
If it weren't for me,
you would have been
killed by those desperadoes.
You've been spying on me.
If not,
why would your men
happen to be there to save me?
I always keep a close eye on
the one I like.
Besides,
you can't even save yourself right now.
As for me,
I am willing
to give you a chance to redeem yourself.
Mr. Alex, are you
willing to cooperate?
Have a rest.
What's the date today?
March 16.
Until you are fully recovered,
don't even think about leaving here.
Ten days left.
I must get better
and escape from this place.
Hello, Boss.
Jiang Yu, I will protect Cloudsea for you.
And I will never spare those
who harmed you.